<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<helpItems xmlns="http://msh" schema="maml">
	<!--All Commands-->
	<command:command xmlns:maml="http://schemas.microsoft.com/maml/2004/10" xmlns:command="http://schemas.microsoft.com/maml/dev/command/2004/10" xmlns:dev="http://schemas.microsoft.com/maml/dev/2004/10">
  <command:details>
		<command:name>zEngine.ps1</command:name>
  </command:details>
  <maml:description>
    <maml:para>zEngine provides a tool to combine tasks that need to be performed in sequence to support a business or IT process.  Please note attribute names and values are case sensitive when using the "import" feature.</maml:para>
  </maml:description>
  <command:syntax>
    <command:syntaxItem>
		<maml:name>zEngine.ps1</maml:name>
	</command:syntaxItem>
  </command:syntax>
  <command:parameters>
    <maml:para>
	'.PARAMETER Path
    Path to the XML playbook to execute. (Mandatory/Validated with Test-Path)
    
    .PARAMETER Cred
    Provide a credential object to execute individual tasks with. (Optional)
    
    .PARAMETER Secret
    The Secret parameter take a username and will attempt to create a Credential object from Secret Server. (Optional)

    .PARAMETER PassThru
    An optional parameter which will return the native powershell objects from each module. (Optional)'
	</maml:para>
  </command:parameters>
  <command:inputTypes>
    <!--Add input type information here-->
  </command:inputTypes>
  <command:returnValues>
    <!--Add return value information here-->
  </command:returnValues>
  <maml:alertSet>
    <!--Add Note information here-->
  </maml:alertSet>
  <command:examples>
    <maml:para>
	'.Example
    zEngine.ps1 -path robotstart.xml
    
    If no additional parameters other than path are specified the script will prompt for a credential set to use.  This command will process robotstart.xml, importing any other XML documents as needed.
    
    
    .Example
    zEngine.ps1 -path robotstart.xml -credential $cred
    
    Runs the script with a specified set of credentials for remote commands.
    
    
    .Example
    zEngine.ps1 -path robotstart.xml -credential $cred -PassThru
    
    Runs the script with a specified set of credentials for remote commands and will return the native powershell objects provided by each module.  Useful for reporting an potentially pipeline applications.
    
    
    .Example
    zEngine.ps1 -path robotstart.xml -credential $cred -verbose
	
    Runs the script with a specified set of credentials for remote commands and will display the native powershell objects provided by each module in the verbose stream'
	</maml:para>
  </command:examples>
  <maml:relatedLinks>
    <!--Add links to related content here-->
  </maml:relatedLinks>
</command:command>